<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>JupyterLab on Daniel Dominguez Chavez</title>
    <link>https://d9dch.github.io/Daniel_Chavez/tags/jupyterlab/</link>
    <description>Recent content in JupyterLab on Daniel Dominguez Chavez</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://d9dch.github.io/Daniel_Chavez/tags/jupyterlab/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Solar Power: Linear Regression Utility</title>
      <link>https://d9dch.github.io/Daniel_Chavez/projects/solar_linear_regression/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://d9dch.github.io/Daniel_Chavez/projects/solar_linear_regression/</guid>
      <description>Project Specifications This was an completely optional project for the Data Science for Energy and Power class at Texas A&amp;amp;M. In addition to machine learning, this class focused on time predictive techniques and methodology such as ARMA, SVD, and K-means.
As many consumers begin to move to solar, it is hard to accurately measure the impact of number of panels vs the environmental benefits a solar array create. Many companies might stretch the truth about efficacy, while others may be more conservative in their estimates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Traffic Stop Racial and Gender Bias in Texas</title>
      <link>https://d9dch.github.io/Daniel_Chavez/projects/traffic_stop_gender_bias/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://d9dch.github.io/Daniel_Chavez/projects/traffic_stop_gender_bias/</guid>
      <description>Project Specifications This was the midterm project for a class on Computational Data Science taught by Dr. Jin Tao, a Data Science Guru and excellent researcher at Texas A&amp;amp;M.
As someone who has personally been affected by both systemic and explicit racism, I chose this project with a real interest in the finds. The goal of this project was to identify biases in policing during traffic stops during 2010-2016 in TEXAS.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>