<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pandas on Daniel Dominguez Chavez</title>
    <link>https://d9dch.github.io/Daniel_Chavez/tags/pandas/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pandas on Daniel Dominguez Chavez</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://d9dch.github.io/Daniel_Chavez/tags/pandas/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Capstone: Machine Learning for Active Shooter events</title>
      <link>https://d9dch.github.io/Daniel_Chavez/projects/machine-learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://d9dch.github.io/Daniel_Chavez/projects/machine-learning/</guid>
      <description>Project Specifications Some Notes about capstone This project was built mainly using Python, Python packages, Tensoflow and Raspberry Pi. All students in the Electrical Engineering program at Texas A&amp;amp;M must complete a sponsored 2 semester capstone program. This is a very involved program usually involving 30-40 hrs of work each week. Each week included constant reporting to supervisors, oral presentations, and laboratory work. While the project is a group project, here I talk about my work on the project, and I how I helped the other members when needed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coulomb Force predictions from chemical makeup</title>
      <link>https://d9dch.github.io/Daniel_Chavez/projects/molecule_linear_regression/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://d9dch.github.io/Daniel_Chavez/projects/molecule_linear_regression/</guid>
      <description>Project Details This is the final project for ECEN 489, an elective course in Computational Data Science. This class in taught by Dr. Jin Tao, and incredible researcher at the high computing center at Texas A&amp;amp;M.
Measurements at the atomic level are incredibly difficult, but of extreme relevance in the study of material sciences. One of the fundamental Measurements is that of Coulomb Force. It is an equation that gives you total force of 2 electrical charges affecting each other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Solar Power: Linear Regression Utility</title>
      <link>https://d9dch.github.io/Daniel_Chavez/projects/solar_linear_regression/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://d9dch.github.io/Daniel_Chavez/projects/solar_linear_regression/</guid>
      <description>Project Specifications This was an completely optional project for the Data Science for Energy and Power class at Texas A&amp;amp;M. In addition to machine learning, this class focused on time predictive techniques and methodology such as ARMA, SVD, and K-means.
As many consumers begin to move to solar, it is hard to accurately measure the impact of number of panels vs the environmental benefits a solar array create. Many companies might stretch the truth about efficacy, while others may be more conservative in their estimates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Traffic Stop Racial and Gender Bias in Texas</title>
      <link>https://d9dch.github.io/Daniel_Chavez/projects/traffic_stop_gender_bias/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://d9dch.github.io/Daniel_Chavez/projects/traffic_stop_gender_bias/</guid>
      <description>Project Specifications This was the midterm project for a class on Computational Data Science taught by Dr. Jin Tao, a Data Science Guru and excellent researcher at Texas A&amp;amp;M.
As someone who has personally been affected by both systemic and explicit racism, I chose this project with a real interest in the finds. The goal of this project was to identify biases in policing during traffic stops during 2010-2016 in TEXAS.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>